proteinsindia.com 2016-04-11

# Privacy Policy | protein supplements online | buy protein supplements online | buy protein powder online

We value the trust that you have placed in us by providing us the information about yourself. This policy sets forth how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide us and would help you in making informed decisions when you use our site and our products.

## **What information do we gather?**

  * **Information that you provide us**

You need to provide us your personal information in order to receive further information about our products. For example, you need to provide us your name, email address and location. If you correspond to us through email, we store the content of your email along with our response.

  * **Information about web site usage**

Apart from the personal information that you provide us, we also collect information about the way you browse through our web site by using the web server logs. Our web site also uses the standard technology named “cookies”.We use these technologies to gather the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, and time spent at our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis and not on the individual basis.

  * **We use Google Analytics that collects data anonymously for statistical and analytical purposes only.**

## **How do we use the personal information provided to us?**

We use the personal information provided to us for responding to your requests, customizing the web pages for you, improving our web stores features, and communicating with you. Sometimes, we may also use your information to inform you about the new services and special offers available at our web site. You may choose to notify us, in case you do not wish to receive these offers.

## **Cookies, what are they?**

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by the web browser on the hard drive and help in uniquely identifying the device from which the website is visited. Cookies do remember the information accessed on a web page which helps to simplify subsequent visits to that web page by the same user.

**How is the Information collected from Cookies and Web Server Logs used?**

Cookies help us in collecting important technical and business statistics about how the user’s use our website and the path do they follow while moving from one page to another.This information assists us in designing a user friendly and easy to use web site for better shopping experience.

Web Server logs give us the count of how many people visited our web site and evaluate our web site’s performance

## **Notification about new services**

We may use the information provided to us to notify you of the new services or any important changes made to our web site.

## **Information Safety Practices**

Our business practices and operations are periodically reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality and security of the information. We restrict the access of personally identifiable data and disclosure of such information only to authorized persons and processes.

## **Disclosing Information to Third Parties**

We do not disclose or sell personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, to the third parties. We may provide the aggregate information about our sales, Web site traffic statistics, customers and related Web site information to our business affiliates.

## **Legally Compelled to Disclose the Information**

We may disclose the personal information if we are legally compelled to do so, in good faith, that the law enforcement offices need this information for reasonable reasons.

## **Links to Other Web Sites**

Our website is not responsible for the content or the practices followed by the web sites linked to and from our website. When you navigate away from our web site to any other web site, our privacy policy is no longer in effect. Please refer to that web site’s privacy policy before proceeding.

## **Your Consent**

By the mere use of our website, you express your consent towards the use and disclosure of your personal information by our web site in accordance with our privacy policy. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time. We would post the changes to our web site. Please review the privacy policy at regular intervals.
